life is filled with interesting things
that's why I could never commit suicide
I'm having too much fun keeping an eye
on you folks watching what you do human
behavior that's what I like humans do
some really interesting things like
besides killing ourselves we also kill
each other murder and we're the only
ones who do that by the way humans are
the only species on earth that
deliberately kills members of another
species for personal gain or pleasure
sometimes you show spawn we're also the
only species that deliberately kills
members of another species for personal
gain or pleasure that's 102 they kill
for pleasure
that's us human beings interesting folks
murderers here's an interesting form of
murder we come up with assassination you
know what's interesting about
assassination well not only does it
change those popularity polls in a big
fuckin hurry well it's also interesting
to notice who it is we assassinate Chiba
knows who it is stop to think of who it
is we kill it's always people who told
us to live together in harmony and try
to love one another
Jesus Gandhi Lincoln John Kennedy Bobby
Kennedy Martin Luther King Medgar Evers
Malcolm X John Lennon they all said try
to live together peacefully BAM right in
the fucking head
apparently we're not ready for that yeah
that's difficult behavior for us not too
bright folks not too fucking right but
if you talk to one of about this guy's
late one time you sit him down
rationally you talk to him about low IQs
and the dumb behavior and the bad
decisions right away they start talking
about education that's the big answer to
everything
education then we need more money for
education we need more books more
teachers more classrooms more schools
but we need more testing for the kids
you said oh well you know we've tried
all of that and the kids still can't
pass the test so I don't you worry about
that we're going to lower the passing
grades after they doing a lot of these
schools now they lower the passing
grades some more kids can pass more kids
pass the school looks good everybody's
happy the IQ of the country slips
another two or three points I'm pretty
soon all you'll need to get into college
is a fucking pencil got a pencil get the
fuck in there it's physics then everyone
wonders why seventeen other countries
graduate more scientists who we do
education politicians know that word to
use it on you politicians have
traditionally hidden behind three things
the flag the Bible and children No Child
Left Behind No Child Left Behind oh
really well it wasn't long ago you were
talking about giving kids a head start
Head Start left behind someone's losing
fucking ground here but there's a reason
there's a reason it's a reason for this
there's a reason education sucks it's
the same reason that it will never ever
ever be fixed it's never going to get
any better don't look for it be happy
with what you got because the owners of
this country don't want that I'm talking
about the real owners now the big reach
of wealthy fact the real owners the big
wealthy business interests that control
things and make all the important
decisions to get the politicians there
they're an irrelevant the politicians
are put there to give you the idea that
you have freedom of choice you don't you
have no choice you have owners they own
you they own everything they own all the
important land they own and control the
corporations they've long since bought
and paid for the Senate the Congress the
state houses the city halls they got the
judges in their back pockets and they
own all the big media
all the big media companies so they
control just about all of the news and
information you get to hear they got you
by the balls they spend billions of
dollars every year lobbying lobbying to
get what they want well we know what
they want they want more for themselves
and less for everybody else but I'll
tell you what they don't want they don't
want a population of citizens capable of
critical thinking they don't want well
informed well educated people capable of
critical thinking they're not interested
in that that doesn't help them that's
against their interests that's right
you know something they don't want
people who are smart enough to sit
around a kitchen table to figure out how
badly they're getting fucked by a system
that threw them overboard thirty fucking
years ago they don't want that you know
what they want they want obedient
workers obedient workers people who are
just smart enough to run the machines
and do the paperwork and just dumb
enough to passively accept all these
increasingly shittier jobs with the
lower pay the longer hours to reduce
benefits the end of overtime and the
vanishing pension that disappears the
minute you go to collect it and now
they're coming for your Social Security
money they want your fuckin retirement
money they want it back so they can give
it to their criminal friends on Wall
Street and you know something they'll
get it they'll get it all from you
sooner or later because they own this
fucking place it's a big club and you
ain't in it you and I are not in the big
club by the way it's the same big club
they use to beat over the head with all
day long when they tell you what to
believe
all day long beating over the head in
their media telling you what to believe
what to think and what to buy the table
is tilted folks the game is rigged and
nobody seems to notice nobody seems to
care good honest hard-working people
white-collar blue-collar doesn't matter
what color shirt you have on good honest
hard-working people continue these are
people of modest means continue to elect
these rich cock suckers who don't give a
fuck about them they don't give a fuck
about you they don't give a fuck about
you they don't care about you at all
and
you know and nobody seems to notice
nobody seems to care that's what the
honors count on the fact that Americans
will probably remain willfully ignorant
of the big red white and blue dick
that's being jammed up their assholes
everyday
because the owners of this country know
the truth it's called the American dream
because you have to be asleep to believe
it but say what you want about American
folks yeah you can say what you want
about Americans you can call the smart
dumb ignorant innocent naive gullible
easily led whatever you want you're
going to have to deal with them you're
going to have to deal with them because
you're in the television business now
you got the all suicide channel on cable
TV
if you've retired you don't have
anything to worry about third time I
said that I probably say it three more
times see in my line of work you got to
keep repeating things over and over and
over again for the truth to sink in to
kind of catapult the propaganda
[Music]
so I hear the voices and I read the
front page and I know the speculation
but I'm the decider and I decide what is
best and what's best for Don Rumsfeld
[Music]
you